Guide to the Jesse H. Jones Corporate and Property records, 1836-2008 MS 621
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Corporate Records, 206870
  - Worth Properties, 231156
    - Book of Account (I), 1934-1942; 231157 (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - Book of Account (II), 1934-1942; 231158 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - Transfer Ledgers, 1934-1942; 231159 (Box 102, Folder 21)
      - Transfer Ledger: Cash Received, 1934-1942; 231160 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      - Transfer Ledger: Disbursements, 1934-1942; 231161 (Box 101, Folder 5)
      - Transfer Ledger: Accounts Payable, 1934-1942; 231165 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Transfer Ledger: Journal, Bank Statements, 1934-1942; 231166 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Assets, Liabilities, Income, Expenses, 1934-1946; 231162 (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - Delinquet Balances, Notes Receivable, 1934-1941; 231163 (Box 102, Folder 23)
    - L+P, 1942-1946; 231164 (Box 102, Folder 24)
    - Transfer Ledger (I), 1937-1946; 231170 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Transfer Ledger (II), 1937-1946; 231171 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Transfer Ledger (III), 1937-1946; 231172 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Accounts Receivable Transfer Ledger, 1938-1944; 231173 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Accounts Receivable Transfer Ledger, 1938-1944; 231174 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Accounts, 1942-1946; 231175 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Transfer Ledger no. 2, 1942-1946; 231176 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      - Transfer Ledger no. 2: Cash Received, 1942-1946; 231167 (Box 103, Folder 3)
      - Transfer Ledger no. 2: Disbursements, Accounts Payable, 1942-1946; 231168 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      - Transfer Ledger no. 2: Journal, Bank Statements, 1942-1946; 231169 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Income Statements, 1935-1939; 231177 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Income Taxes, 1934-1944; 231178 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Income Taxes, 1945-1946; 231179 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Minute Book, 1934-1946; 231180 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Stock Book, 1934; 231181 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Trust Deed and Chattle Mortgage, 1934; 231182 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Various Documents, 1933-1964; 231183 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Various Documents, 1939-1947; 231184 (Box 104, Folder 15)
  - Yoakum Lumber, 231185
    - Various Documents, 1904; 231186 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - 10 East 40th Street Building, Inc., 231187
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1933; 231188 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Various Documents, 1954-1955; 231189 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Various Documents, 1954; 231190 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - 1114 Texas Ave. Building, Inc., 231887
      - Cash Receipts, Disbursements, Journal, etc., 1935-1943; 231888 (Box 107, Folder 4)
      - Ledger, 1950 - 1964; 232010 (Box 110, Folder 13)
      - Franchise Taxes, 1949 - 1963; 232011 (Box 110, Folder 14)
      - Income Taxes, 1948 - 1964; 232012 (Box 110, Folder 15)
      - Liquidated into HEI, 9/14/1964; 232013 (Box 110, Folder 16)
      - Minute Book, 1948 - 1964; 232014 (Box 110, Folder 17)
      - Stock Book, 1948; 232016 (Box 110, Folder 18)
  - 40 East 61st Street Corp., 231191
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1927; 231192 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Operation of Expenses, 1945-1954; 231193 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Assets and Reserves, Rents Receivable, Liabilities and Capital, Operating Income, 1945-1954; 231194 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Ledgers; Stock Book, 1951-1954; 1927-1952; 231195 (Box 104, Folder 23)
      - Cash Book, 1951-1954; 231450 (Box 106, Folder 1)
      - Journal, 1954; 231451 (Box 106, Folder 2)
      - Stock Book, 1927-1952; 231453 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Minute Book, 1927-1957; 231403 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - 60 East 65th Street Corp., 231404
    - Franchise Tax, 1954; 231405 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Mayfair House Sale: Appraisal, 1972; 231406 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - (Park Ave. 65th Street Corp.; 612 Park Ave Corp.) Mayfair House Sale: Sale, 1967-1973; 231407 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - (Park Ave. 65th Street Corp.; 612 Park Ave Corp.) Mayfair House Sale: Sale, 1967-1973; 231408 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Various File, 1924; 231409 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Reorganization (I), 1935; 231411 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Reorganization (II), 1935; 231410 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - 200 Madison Avenue Corp, 231412
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1925; 231413 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Various Documents, 1929-1952; 231414 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - 400 East 57th Street Corp., 231415
    - Various Documents, 1930; 231416 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Assets, Liabilities + Capital, Reserves, Income, Expense, 1945-1954; 231417 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Building Service; Heat, Light, and AC; Maintinence; Administration; Fix and Other Expenses; Closed Accounts, 1953-1954; 231418 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Ledgers; Stock Book, 1948-1954; 1930-1954; 231419 (Box 105, Folder 14)
      - Journal vol. 5, 1948-1954; 231463 (Box 106, Folder 4)
      - Cash Book, 1951-1954; 231458 (Box 106, Folder 5)
      - Cash Book, 1953-1954; 231456 (Box 106, Folder 6)
      - Voucher Register, 1953-1954; 231464 (Box 107, Folder 1)
      - Stock Book, 1930-1954; 231466 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Balance Sheets and Operating Statements, 1948; 231420 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Audit Report, 1953; 231421 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Annual Information Return (1096), 1931; 231422 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - New York Real Estate Tax Bills, 1931-1953; 231423 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - New York State Franchise Tax, 1931-1954; 231424 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Capital Stock Tax, 1933-1945; 231425 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - N.Y. State Income Tax- Employees Reports, 1934-1951; 231426 (Box 105, Folder 21)
    - N.Y.C. Utility Tax, 1935-1943; 231427 (Box 105, Folder 22)
    - N.Y.C. Sales Tax, 1935-1954; 231428 (Box 105, Folder 23)
    - N.Y. State Utility Tax, 1937-1943; 231429 (Box 105, Folder 24)
    - N.Y. City Gross Receipts Tax, 1939-1954; 231432 (Box 105, Folder 25)
    - Corporate Excess Profit Tax Return, 1940-1952; 231434 (Box 105, Folder 26)
    - Year End Withholding Tax Statement, 1943-1951; 231435 (Box 105, Folder 27)
    - Payroll Tax Reports, 1944-1954; 231436 (Box 105, Folder 28)
    - Work Sheets, 1949-1954; 231437 (Box 105, Folder 29)
    - Misc Worksheets and Statements, 1941-1947; 231438 (Box 105, Folder data_value_missing_2473fb831858efa6e30dfef2e7b0adcb)
    - Federal Unemployment Insurance, 1939-1959; 231909 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - New York Statement Unemployment Insurance, 1945-1950; 231910 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - N.Y. State Unemployment Insurance Reports, 1948-1954; 231911 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Federal Unemployment Insurance, 1951-1954; 231912 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Depreciation Schedules, 1942-1954; 231913 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Notice of Experience Rating Changes, 1953-1956; 231914 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Restaurant Alteration, 1952; 231915 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Rent Filings, 1955; 231916 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Closing File, 1954; 231917 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Contract of Sale, 1954; 231918 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Sale File, 1954; 231919 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Minute Book, 1930-1954; 231940 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - 612 Park Ave. Corp., 231472
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1935; 231941 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - Stock Book, 1935-1943; 231473 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Specifications, Bldg Alt., Certificate of Occupancy, 1925-1950; 231942 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - (Opperating Mayfair House, NY, NY) Financial Statements, 1957-1971; 231943 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - New York State Franchise Tax, 1954-1954; 231944 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - Income Tax, 1954-1965; 231945 (Box 108, Folder 17)
    - Income Tax, 1966-1971; 231946 (Box 108, Folder 18)
    - Mortgages, 1935-1949; 231947 (Box 108, Folder 19)
    - Mortgage, 1949; 231948 (Box 108, Folder 20)
    - New York City Corporation Tax File, 1970-1971; 231949 (Box 108, Folder 21)
    - Closing Papers in Connection with Refinancing vol. 1, 4/22/1949; 231950 (Box 108, Folder 22)
    - Closing Papers in Connection with Refinancing vol. 2, 4/22/1949; 231951 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Stock Book, 1935-1943; 231952 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Various Documents, 1928-1954; 231953 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Mayfair House, 1943-1944; 231954 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Mayfair House, 231964
    - Correspondence, 1953 - 1954; 231965 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1956; 231966 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1957; 231967 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1958; 231968 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1959; 231969 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1960; 231970 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1961; 231971 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1962; 231972 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1963; 231973 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1964; 231974 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1965; 231975 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1966; 231976 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1967; 231977 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1968; 231978 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1969; 231979 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1970; 231980 (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1971; 231981 (Box 109, Folder 21)
    - Remodeling and Elevator Files, 231982 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1972; 231983 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - New York City - Re: Smoke Stack Repairs, 231984 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Current, 1955; 231985 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Benau, 1957; 231986 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Copies of Unions' Hotel Contract, 1966 + 1969; 231987 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Payroll and Operating Study Report, 1957; 231988 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Pictures of Suite 9B (Endowment), 1957; 231989 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Electical Wiring Contract - Fischback and Moore on Mayfair House, 1969; 231990 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - Certified Statements, Prudential Insurance Co., of America, 231991 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Elevator Modernization, 231992 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - New York - Teruzzi Suit, 231993 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - 1158 Fifth Ave, 232026
    - Various Documents, 232027 (Box 110, Folder 19)
  - American Building Maintenance Co., 232028
    - Various Documents, 1976 - 1991; 232029 (Box 110, Folder 20)
  - Various Corporations, 232030
    - Annual Report of Property Subject to Escheat Filed with State Treasurer, 12/14/1961; 232031 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - Capital Stock Tax Returns, 1933; 232033 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - Capital Stock Tax Returns, 1934 - 1935; 232034 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - Capital Stock Tax Returns, 1936 - 1937; 232035 (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Franchise Taxes, 1929 - 1931; 232038 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Franchise Tax (1 of 2), 1931 - 1961; 232039 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Franchise Tax (2 of 2), 1931 - 1961; 232040 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Income Tax, YE 1913; 232042 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Income Tax, Foster Building and Realty Co., Houston Hotel Asso., 1920 - 1926; 232043 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Consolidated Tax Return, YE 1927; 232044 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Consolidated Tax Return, YE 1928; 232046 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Consolidated Tax Return, YE 1929; 232048 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Consolidated Tax Return, YE 1930; 232049 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Labor Agreements, 1950 - 1954; 232050 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Labor Agreements, 1950 - 1954; 232056 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - J. Mecom Purchase (Uconsummated), 1965 - 1966; 232057 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - J. Mecom Purchase (Uconsummated), 1965 - 1966; 232058 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - J. Mecom Purchase (Uconsummated), 1965 - 1971; 232059 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Notary Bonds, 1951 - 1973; 232063 (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Pension Trust, 1948 - 1954; 232067 (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Stocks and Bonds, 1926 - 1954; 232068 (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - Taxes, 1953 - 1954; 232069 (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - Various Documents, 1901 - 1932; 232070 (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - Various Documents, 1928 - 1956; 232071 (Box 111, Folder 20)
    - New York City, 1947 - 1948; 232072 (Box 111, Folder 21)
    - Document Copies, 1925 - 1927; 232073 (Box 111, Folder 22)
    - Employees, 1953 - 1958; 232074 (Box 111, Folder 23)
    - Forms, 232075 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Capital Stock Tax Returns, 1938 - 1939; 232076 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Capital Stock Tax Returns, 1940 - 1942; 232077 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Capital Stock Tax Returns, 1944 - 1945; 232078 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - LIST, 1958; 232083 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - LIST with Officers, 232085 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Cremation Certificates, 1939 - 1947; 232090 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1919 - 1933; 232093 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1925 - 1933; 232096 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1925 - 1959; 232099 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Pension Trust, 1948 - 1954; 232100 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Various Documents, 1928 - 1957; 232105 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Wage Stabilization, 1945; 232106 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Workmen's Compensation, 1966 - 1974; 232107 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Rental Record (Transfer Ledger) (I), 1941 - 1945; 232140 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Rental Record (Transfer Ledger) (II), 1941 - 1945; 232141 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Rental Record (I), 1946 - 1952; 232142 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Rental Record (II), 1946 - 1952; 232143 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Operating Journal, 1949 - 1954; 232144 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Payroll (I), 1942 - 1944; 232146 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Payroll (II), 1942 - 1944; 232147 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Payroll (III), 1942 - 1944; 232148 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Bankers Mortgage Corp. - Stock Book, 1924 - 1934; 232149 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Fort Worth Properties - Stock Book, 1924 - 1931; 232150 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Dallas Texas Amusement Co. - Minute Book, 1922 - 1933; 232151 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Deepwater Farms - Minute Book, 1917 - 1919; 232156 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Ledger, 1957; 232162 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Various Leases, 232165 (Box 115, Folder data_value_missing_a36640d2f702e2840d539e2c6b62b5e8)
    - Ledger, ND; 232166 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Mr. Heyne's Accumulation File on N.Y. No. 3, 232167 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1980s; 232168 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Various New York Corps., 232118
    - A.B. Jones, 232119 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Fred J. Heyne Accumulation File on NY No. 1 - 10 East 40th Street Building Inc. (I), 232122 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Fred J. Heyne Accumulation File on NY No. 1 - 10 East 40th Street Building Inc. (II), 232123 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Building Data Forwarded to Houston, 232128 (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Data re: Various Buildings, 232134 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Mortgage Interest Rates and Amoritization Schedules, 232136 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - Mr. Heyne's Accumulation File on N.Y. No. 1, 232137 (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Mr. Heyne's Accumulation File on N.Y. No. 2, 232138 (Box 112, Folder 22)
- Series II: Property Records, 234181
  - Angelina County, 234182
    - M.T. Jones, J. Parmer Survey - Translation of Spanish Grant to Parmer, 1834 - 1835; 234183 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Spanish Grant to Smith Translation of Title, 1834 - 1835; 234184 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Smith to Gann, 1838; 234186 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Gann to Phillips, 1839; 234187 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Smith to Phillips, 1839; 234188 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Smith to Smith, Republic of Texas Deed, 1839; 234189 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - M.T. Jones, S. Stanley Survey - Roberts to Jones, 1840; 234190 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Roberts to Edmonds, 1847; 234191 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Bullock Vs. Smith, 1847; 234192 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - M.T. Jones, J. Parmer Survey - Hollinssworth to Stedman, 1858; 234193 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - M.T. Jones, Dodge and James for HT&BRR - Texas Land Grant, 1872; 234194 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - M.T. Jones, Dodge and James for HT&BRR - Texas Land Grants, 1873; 234195 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - M.T. Jones, Various Properties - Bullock to Bullock, 1875; 234196 (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - M.T. Jones, Dodge and James for H.T. & BRR - Texas Land Grant, Sumeral to Dodge 1885, 1875; 234197 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - M.T. Jones, Dodge and James for H.T. & BRR - Texas Land Grants (8), 1875; 234198 (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - M.T. Jones, J. Parmer and Robertson Surveys - Stedman to Rand, 1875; 234199 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - M.T. Jones, J. Parmer Survey - Tax Receipts, 1875 - 1895; 234200 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - M.T. Jones, SA & MG RR - McIntosh to Lock, 1878, 1893; 234201 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - M.T. Jones, Runnels Survey - Runnels to Hensarling, 1882; 234202 (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - M.T. Jones, J.T. Smith Survey - Texas Land Grant, 1882; 234203 (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - M.T. Jones, J.T. Smith Survey - Smith to Branch, 1882; 234204 (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Jones to Prescott, 1882; 234205 (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - M.T. Jones, Runnels Survey - Abstracts, 1882 - 1895; 234206 (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Ayres to Bullock, Gann to Roberts and Phillips, 1882 - 1895; 234207 (Box 116, Folder 25)
    - M.T. Jones, E. P. Fuller Survey - Texas Land Grant, 1886; 234208 (Box 116, Folder 26)
    - M.T. Jones, E. P. Fuller Survey - Abstract, 1886 - 1895; 234209 (Box 116, Folder 27)
    - M.T. Jones, J.T. Smith Survey - Branch and Towsend to Herndon, 1887; 234210 (Box 116, Folder 28)
    - M.T. Jones, Blum Survey - Abstract, 1887 - 1894; 234211 (Box 116, Folder 29)
    - M.T. Jones, E.P. Fuller Survey - Hensarling to McIver, 1888; 234212 (Box 116, Folder 30)
    - M.T. Jones, Runnels Survey - Hensarling to McIver, 1888; 234213 (Box 116, Folder 31)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Bullock to Smith, 1889 - 1890; 234214 (Box 116, Folder 32)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - W.S. Smith to Bullock, Bullock Power of Attorney, 1890; 234215 (Box 116, Folder 33)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Bullock to Kelty, 1890; 234216 (Box 116, Folder 34)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Vendor's Liens, Kelty to Irvin, 1890; 234217 (Box 116, Folder 35)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Kelty to Irvin, 1890; 234218 (Box 116, Folder 36)
    - M.T. Jones, Runnels Survey - Tax Receipts, 1890 - 1895; 234219 (Box 116, Folder 37)
    - M.T. Jones, Business Documents, 1891 - 1897; 234220 (Box 116, Folder 38)
    - M.T. Jones, J.H. Chapman - Texas Land Grant, 1892; 234221 (Box 116, Folder 39)
    - M.T. Jones, E. Brown Survey - Mansfield Release to Chapman, 1892 - 1894; 234222 (Box 116, Folder 40)
    - M.T. Jones, E. P. Fuller Survey - Tax Receipts, 1892 - 1895; 234223 (Box 116, Folder 41)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Irvin to MT Jones, 1892; 234224 (Box 116, Folder 42)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Jones-Carter Agreement, 1893; 234225 (Box 116, Folder 43)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Land Sales, 1893; 234226 (Box 116, Folder 44)
    - M.T. Jones, S. Johnson Survey - Collier to MT Jones, 1893; 234227 (Box 116, Folder 45)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Smith Heirs to MT Jones, Pert Correspondence, 1893; 234228 (Box 116, Folder 46)
    - M.T. Jones, J.F. Gilbert Survey - Land Sales, 1893; 234229 (Box 116, Folder 47)
    - M.T. Jones, S. Johnson Survey - Collier to Townsend, 1893; 234230 (Box 116, Folder 48)
    - M.T. Jones, S. Johnson Survey - Collier to Townsend, 1893; 234231 (Box 116, Folder 49)
    - M.T. Jones, S. Johnson Survey - Townsend to MT Jones, 1893; 234232 (Box 116, Folder 50)
    - M.T. Jones, Letter of Instruction to Mantooth and Townsend - MT Jones Handwritten Letter, 1893; 234233 (Box 116, Folder 51)
    - M.T. Jones, Dodge and James for HT&BRR - Dodge Estate to MT Jones, 1893 - 1897; 234234 (Box 116, Folder 52)
    - M.T. Jones, Dodge and James for HT&BRR - Tract Lists, Estimates, 1893 - 1898; 234235 (Box 116, Folder 53)
    - M.T. Jones, Timber Estimates, 1893 - 1899; 234236 (Box 116, Folder 54)
    - M.T. Jones, Blum Survey - Mantooth to Jones, 1894; 234237 (Box 116, Folder 55)
    - M.T. Jones, E. Brown Survey - Chapman to Jones, 1894; 234238 (Box 116, Folder 56)
    - M.T. Jones, Property Inventory, 1894; 234239 (Box 116, Folder 57)
    - M.T. Jones, Cherry Survey - Herrington et al to Herrington, 2 Tracts, 1895; 234240 (Box 116, Folder 58)
    - M.T. Jones, Fulcher Survey - Calley to Manstooth and Towsend, 1895; 234241 (Box 116, Folder 59)
    - M.T. Jones; Fuller Survey and Runnels Survey - McIver Power of Attorney, 1895; 234242 (Box 116, Folder 61)
    - M.T. Jones, J. Parmer Survey - Rand to Mantooth and Towsend, 1895; 234243 (Box 116, Folder 62)
    - M.T. Jones, Runnels Survey - Fuller to Hensarling, 1895; 234244 (Box 116, Folder 63)
    - M.T. Jones, Runnels Survey - Harvard to Jones, 1895; 234245 (Box 116, Folder 64)
    - M.T. Jones, Runnels Survey - McIver to Jones, 1895; 234246 (Box 116, Folder 65)
    - M.T. Jones, Towsend Survey - Texas Land Grant, 1895; 234247 (Box 116, Folder 66)
    - M.T. Jones, Towsend Survey - Townsend to Jones, 1895; 234248 (Box 116, Folder 67)
    - M.T. Jones, Tax Receipts, 1896 - 1899; 234249 (Box 116, Folder 68)
    - M.T. Jones, Timber Deeds, 1897; 234250 (Box 116, Folder 69)
    - M.T. Jones, Timber Deeds, 1897; 234251 (Box 116, Folder 69)
    - M.T. Jones, J. Parmer - Timber Report, 1897; 234252 (Box 116, Folder 70)
    - M.T. Jones, J. Parmer Survey - Mantooth and Towsend to Jones, 1897; 234253 (Box 116, Folder 71)
    - M.T. Jones, Timber Sales, 1897; 234254 (Box 116, Folder 72)
    - M.T. Jones, Cherry Survey - Bullitt to MT Jones, 1898; 234258 (Box 116, Folder 73)
    - M.T. Jones, Cherry Survey - Herringten et al to Herringten, 1898; 234259 (Box 116, Folder 74)
    - M.T. Jones, Cherry Survey - Herrington to Jones, 1898; 234260 (Box 116, Folder 75)
    - M.T. Jones, Mantooth Survey - Mantooth to MT Jones, 1898; 234261 (Box 116, Folder 76)
    - M.T. Jones, Holdings Lists, 1898; 234262 (Box 116, Folder 77)
    - M.T. Jones, Scarborough Survey - Burch to MT Jones, 1898; 234263 (Box 116, Folder 78)
    - M.T. Jones, A. Shields Survey - Qilland to MT Jones, 1898; 234264 (Box 116, Folder 79)
    - M.T. Jones, J.T. Smith Survey - Herndon to MT Jones, 1898; 234265 (Box 116, Folder 80)
    - M.T. Jones, T. Smith Survey - Starr to MT Jones, 1898; 234266 (Box 116, Folder 81)
    - M.T. Jones, MT Jones Survey - Texas Land Grants (2), 1898 - 1899; 234267 (Box 116, Folder 82)
    - M.T. Jones, Timber Deeds, 1898 - 1899; 234268 (Box 116, Folder 83)
    - M.T. Jones, Dodge and James for HT&BRR, 1916 - 1920; 234269 (Box 116, Folder 84)
    - M.T. Jones, Fulcher Survey- W.E. Jones to MT Jones Estate, 1899; 234296 (Box 116, Folder 85)
    - M.T. Jones, Sawmill Agreement, 1899; 234297 (Box 116, Folder 86)
    - M.T. Jones, S. Stanley Survey- MT Jones Estate to Temple, 234298 (Box 116, Folder 87)
    - M.T. Jones, S. Stanley Survey- Mantooth and Townsend to TW House, 1899; 234299 (Box 116, Folder 88)
    - M.T. Jones, Abstract 594, Survey #3- Mt Jones Estate to Cameron, 1899; 234300 (Box 116, Folder 89)
    - M.T. Jones, None Mills Property- Various Lands, MT Jones Estate to N. Mills, 1900; 234301 (Box 116, Folder 90)
    - M.T. Jones, Tax Receipts, 1900-1912; 234303 (Box 116, Folder 91)
    - M.T. Jones, MT Jones Estate Survey- Texas Land Grant, 1902; 234304 (Box 116, Folder 92)
    - M.T. Jones, Delinquent Taxes, 1908; 234471 (Box 116, Folder 93)
    - Louisa Jones, M.T. Jones Estate, 1905-1908; 234305 (Box 116, Folder 94)
    - Louisa Jones, M.T. Jones Estate, 1915-1921; 234472 (Box 116, Folder 95)
    - Misc Timberlands, 1912; 234473 (Box 116, Folder 96)
    - Tax Receipts, 1914-1921; 234474 (Box 116, Folder 97)
    - JL Qunalty League, 1924-1946; 234257 (Box 116, Folder 98)
  - Angelina and Cherokee Counties, 234475